nationalledger.com 2010-10-25

# Privacy Policy - National Ledger

UPDATED: January 7, 2010

Internet user privacy is of the highest importance to The National Ledger. The National Ledger is committed to protecting your privacy. The National Ledger does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as name, address, email address or telephone number, from visitors to our website. 

**Cookies:**

The National Ledger may use cookies during your visit to the web site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user's computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site, such as advertisers, however we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Third Party Advertising and Content:**

Our website contains links to websites that are not operated by The National Ledger, and also receives content from third parties. The National Ledger makes no representations about the privacy practices of these third party sites. Be aware that during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame that includes National Ledger content, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party.

Users should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties if providing personally identifiable information.

The National Ledger also uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies and information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements that may be of interest to you. This is known as Online Behavior Advertising ("O.B.A") and/or Multi-Site Advertising. The information they use is not personally identifiable, and does not contain your name, email address, physical address, or phone number.

To get more information or to opt out please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Privacy Protection for Children:**

This policy describes the privacy practices of The National Ledger relating to information collected from children. This privacy policy does not apply to third party web sites, or to companies and persons that are not controlled by, affiliated with or managed by The National Ledger. The National Ledger does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age. 

The National Ledger feels strongly about protecting the privacy of children. We encourage kids to involve their parents in any interactive activity they participate in online. Except where otherwise disclosed, we will not collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of thirteen without obtaining express parental consent. All general information collected from users under the age of thirteen is used only for aggregate statistical analysis. 

**Changes:**

The National Ledger reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy:**

By using The National Ledger sites and services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy Statement. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Policy Statement, your only remedy is to discontinue use of The National Ledger sites. We reserve the right, to modify this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. If we materially change how we use your personal information we will notify through a prominent notice on this Privacy Policy Statement of the web site. Your continued use of any portion of The National Ledger sites following notification or posting of such changes, will constitute your accept of those changes. Questions or concerns about our specific policies, please contact us through our feedback form.

**Contact:**

Direct any questions to us via e-mail.

_Or mail us at:_

The National Ledger  
PO Box 1212  
Apache Junction, AZ 85117-1212
